additionalmedia.com 2008-12-01

# Additional Media, Stategy, Creativity, Insight through affordable solutions

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

The Additional Media privacy policy governs the way in which we process any personal information that you provide to us. We will notify you if the way in which we process your information is to change at any time.

You can access our home page and browse our site without disclosing any personal data except for information automatically collected by cookies that we use (see below).

**Who may process data**

Your personal information, which includes your name, address and any other details you provide to us which concern you as an individual, may be processed both by us and by other companies within our group for the purposes of fulfilling your order. Each of the companies authorised to process your information as mentioned above will do so in accordance with this privacy policy.

**Purpose of processing**

We will use your information for the purpose of fulfilling orders placed by you, processing any other transactions authorised or made by you with us, informing you of special offers and providing other marketing information to you which we think you may find of interest and for the purpose of undertaking product or customer research and development.

**Disclosure of information**

In the unlikely event that a liquidator, administrator or receiver is appointed your information may be transferred to a third party purchaser of the business provided that purchaser undertakes to use your information for the same purposes as set out in this policy. We undertake not to provide your personal information to any third parties except in accordance with this policy.

Your information will not be disclosed to government or local authorities or other government institutions except as required by law or other binding regulations.

**Cookies**

We may send a small file to your computer when you visit our website. This will enable us to identify you on future visits and to track your movement within it for 'user-friendly' development purposes. We may use cookies to collect and store data and to link information stored by them with the personal data you supply to us. Except for the use of cookies, we only collect  information you specifically provide to us. You can set your computer browser to reject cookies but this may preclude your use of certain parts of this website.

**Security**

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorised access, improper use and disclosure, unauthorised destruction or accidental loss.

**Access to information**

You may ask us whether we are storing personal information about you by emailing us and, if you wish, we will provide you with a copy of any personal data we hold about you. We may ask for proof of your identity before providing any information and reserve the right to refuse to provide any information if identity is not established.
